const summaries = {
  moonlighter: {
    quote:
      "During a long-passed archaeological excavation, a set of Gates were discovered. People quickly realized that these ancient passages lead to different realms and dimensions – providing brave and reckless adventurers with treasures beyond measure. Rynoka, a small commercial village, was founded near the excavation site providing refuge and a place for adventurers to sell their hard-earned riches.",
    image: "post/moonlighter/Will.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Action RPG",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Will, the shopkeeper",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "MacOS",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "May 29, 2018",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "25 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "DLC Completion",
        answer: "50%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Combat, economy",
      },
      {
        question: "Weak points",
        answer: "Story, quests",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes, absolutely",
      },
    ],
  },
  cateau: {
    quote:
      "Set in Paris, <em class='game-title'>Cateau</em> is a visual novel that takes the idea of friendship and investigates it through a particular lens – what it might take to actually be a friend in more than concept alone. As the protagonist, you come to understand that your friend and roommate Roselle is unwell. You take it upon yourself to try and rekindle that spark of life that seems to have gone out by engaging in one of her former interests, cats.",
    image: "post/cateau/PeeWee.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Visual Novel",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Player-insert",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "Windows",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Oct 17, 2018",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "1 hour",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Artwork, background music, choices matter",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes, if you like cats and short visual novels!",
      },
    ],
  },
  tacoma: {
    quote:
      "<em class='game-title'>Tacoma</em> is a narrative adventure set aboard a high-tech space station in the year 2088. As you go about your mission, you’ll explore every detail of how the station’s crew lived and worked, finding the clues that add up to a gripping story of trust, fear, and resolve in the face of disaster.",
    image: "post/tacoma/amy.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Narrative driven exploration walking simulator",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: 'Amitjyoti "Amy" Ferrier, a data retrieval agent',
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "Windows",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Aug 2, 2017",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "3 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Relationships, diverse cast, the moments in between",
      },
      {
        question: "Weak Points",
        answer: "May be a bit predictable",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer:
          "Yes, for those who like sci-fi and don't mind the lack of action",
      },
    ],
  },
  riskofrain: {
    quote:
      "<em class='game-title'>Risk of Rain</em> is an action platformer with roguelike elements. With permanent death as a primary feature, players will have to play their best to get as far as possible. Fight on a mysterious planet with randomly spawning enemies and bosses, either alone or with 3 friends in online co-op.",
    image: "post/riskofrain/commando.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Action roguelike platformer, co-op",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "12 unlockable characters",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "Windows, MacOS",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Nov 8, 2013",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "103 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "80%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Items, balance, characters",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes, especially if you like a lot of death",
      },
    ],
  },
  coffeetalk: {
    quote:
      "<em class='game-title'>Coffee Talk</em> is a game about listening to people’s problems and helping them by serving up a warm drink out of the ingredients you have in stock. It is a game that depicts lives as humanly as possible, while having a cast that is more than just humans.",
    image: "post/coffeetalk/neil.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Fantasy visual novel",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Player-insert barista (I named mine Mango)",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "Nintendo Switch",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Jan 28, 2020",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "5 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100% story-wise, 0% endless mode",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Pixel art, characters, chill atmosphere, LGBTQ+",
      },
      {
        question: "Weak Points",
        answer:
          "Some story mode recipes have no hints on how to make them, ending seems a little abrupt (I want more!!)",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes!!!",
      },
    ],
  },
  thenightoftherabbit: {
    quote:
      "Lose yourself in a tale of magic and wonder, where anything is possible and where nothing is quite as it seems; join young Jerry and follow a peculiar white rabbit to the wondrous realm of Mousewood, a land where critters can speak and where mystery abounds.",
    image: "post/nightoftherabbit/magician.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Point-and-click fantasy adventure",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "A young boy named Jerry Hazelnut",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "Windows",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "May 28, 2013",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "13 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Storybook writing, charming music, beautiful art",
      },
      {
        question: "Weak Points",
        answer:
          "The challenges could be a little hard to solve without outside help",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer:
          "Yes, for fans of point-and-click adventures with a bit of childhood nostalgia",
      },
    ],
  },
  eliza: {
    quote:
      "<em class='game-title'>Eliza</em> is a visual novel about an AI counseling program, the people who develop it, and the people who use it. Follow Evelyn Ishino-Aubrey as she reconnects with people from her past, gets to know the people of Seattle who use Eliza for counseling, and decides the course of her future.",
    image: "post/eliza/evelyn.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Visual novel",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Eliza, a software architect",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "MacOS",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Aug 12, 2019",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "4 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Story, relevancy",
      },
      {
        question: "Weak Points",
        answer: "Not much control, some endings",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes, especially for tech workers and urbanites",
      },
    ],
  },
  aviaryattorney: {
    quote:
      "The year is 1848. Paris is on the brink of yet another revolution, and the prisons are overflowing with guilty and innocent alike. One man stands for justice amid society's chaos. No. One bird... Play the role of Monsieur Jayjay Falcon, a bird of prey with a good heart and questionable lawyering expertise. Join him and his witty apprentice, Sparrowson, as the two take on clients, interview witnesses, collect evidence, and deliver justice to the guilty.",
    image: "post/aviaryattorney/jayjay.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Historical mystery visual novel",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "A bird lawyer named Jayjay Falcon",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "Windows",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Dec 22, 2015",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "7 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Enthralling storyline, hilarious dialogue, choices matter",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes, for fans of detective games (especially Ace Attorney)!",
      },
    ],
  },
  cardofdarkness: {
    quote:
      "Many stacks of cards lie before you filled with monsters, treasures, weapons, potions, and spells. You can only see the top card of each stack — what lies beneath is a mystery. Cast powerful spells, slay fantastic monsters, discover ancient secrets, and ultimately save the world — just by picking up the right cards. Card of Darkness is a full-featured adventure designed around an accessible, minimalist, card game core.",
    image: "post/cardofdarkness/cod.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Card-based roguelike",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Zach Gage, Pendleton Ward",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "You, the Hero",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "iOS",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Oct 7, 2019",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "15 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Illustration, animations, bosses",
      },
      {
        question: "Weak Points",
        answer: "Quite possibly none",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes, especially for those who love games but have little time",
      },
    ],
  },
  tangletower: {
    quote:
      "Unravel a thrilling mystery by exploring a strange and twisted mansion, discovering curious clues, interrogating peculiar suspects and solving unique puzzles. Freya Fellow has been murdered. The lead suspect? A shadowy figure found looming over her body, wielding a knife. The problem? That suspect... is just a painting.",
    image: "post/tangletower/grimoire.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Point-and-click murder mystery",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "SFB Games",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "The detective Grimoire and his sidekick Sally",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "MacOS, iOS",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Sep 19, 2019",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "6 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer:
          "Art, story, character personality, dialogue, puzzle difficulty",
      },
      {
        question: "Weak Points",
        answer: "Slightly rushed ending",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes, yes, yes!",
      },
    ],
  },
  fortheking: {
    quote:
      "<em class='game-title'>For The King</em> is a Procedural Turn-Based RPG that features Solo and Co-op play. Featuring a blend of Roguelike, Boardgame and JRPG Combat mechanics, For The King has a unique feel and aesthetic. Players must survive cunning enemies and creatures, wicked weather and brutal traps in their quest to solve the mysterious death of the king and bring order to the land.",
    image: "post/fortheking/fortheking.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Turn-based, co-op, roguelike RPG",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "IronOak Games",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "1-3 adventurers",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "Windows",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Feb 28, 2017",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "27 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Quirky classes, challenging, think before you act!",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes, for fans of more traditional tabletop RPGs",
      },
    ],
  },
  takeshiandhiroshi: {
    quote:
      "<em class='game-title'>Takeshi and Hiroshi</em> combines the two worlds of puppet animation and Role Playing Game. It tells the story of two brothers and their daily life. The 14-year-old Takeshi, a game designer to-be, is creating a game for his weak little brother Hiroshi who always wants to play the next chapter of the game as soon as possible. As the game is still in the making, Takeshi has to improvise and secretly plays some of the monster roles himself.",
    image: "post/takeshiandhiroshi/takeshi.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Visual novel, strategy RPG",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Oink Games",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Takeshi... and Hiroshi",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "iOS",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Nov 1, 2019",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "3 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Story, puppet animation",
      },
      {
        question: "Weak Points",
        answer: "Repetitiveness, not much need for real strategy",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes, for the story. No, for the gameplay.",
      },
    ],
  },
  darksidedetective: {
    quote:
      "Join The <em class='game-title'>Darkside Detective</em>, Francis McQueen, as he investigates the bizarre, the supernatural and those missing cat cases that keep getting dropped on his desk.",
    image: "post/darksidedetective/francismcqueen.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Point-and-click mystery",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Spooky Doorway",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Francis McQueen",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "Windows",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Jul 27, 2017",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "5 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Humor, quirky cases, puzzles",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes, especially if you like comedy!",
      },
    ],
  },
  detectivegui: {
    quote:
      "Following the adventures of Barky, <em class='game-title'>Detective GUI</em> is a quick, creative puzzle platformer that asks the player to think outside the box.",
    image: "post/detectivegui/barky.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Puzzle platformer",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Joqlepecheur",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Detective Barky",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "Browser",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "May 13, 2020",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "1 hour",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Ingenuity, potential",
      },
      {
        question: "Weak Points",
        answer: "Short length",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "To any puzzle enthusiasts who want a quick fix",
      },
    ],
  },
  windingworlds: {
    quote:
      "You're far from home. You're not sure how you got here. But you do know one thing: it's your calling to help your new friends, however you can. But not all of them are being cooperative... From the award-winning studio that brought you GNOG comes <em class='game-title'>Winding Worlds</em>, a finger-wiggling puzzle-adventure about a girl, a Wurm, and how to say goodbye.",
    image: "post/windingworlds/willow.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Point-and-click puzzle adventure",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "KO_OP",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Willow, guided by Wurm",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "MacOS, iOS",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "May 15, 2020",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "2 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Art, unique puzzle solving, story, message",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer:
          "Without a doubt, especially if you need some motivation or inspiration and are down to do some soul searching",
      },
    ],
  },
  dontopenyoureyes: {
    quote:
      "You are trying to fall asleep. In the midst of a silent night, a shadowy being approaches your bed. You can't see it... but across the darkness of your eyelids, a silhouette forms nonetheless. It seeks one thing: for you to open your eyes, and tell them how they look. Will you comply? Or will you refuse to see them for what they are? The choice is yours.",
    image: "post/dontopenyoureyes/demon.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Horror visual novel",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Daniel “Via” Cuturrufo",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "You",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "Windows",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Mar 29, 2019",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "1 hour",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Sound design, immersion",
      },
      {
        question: "Weak Points",
        answer: "Sharp immersion dropoff",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "To any horror visual novel fans with free time",
      },
    ],
  },
  oldmansjourney: {
    quote:
      "<em class='game-title'>Old Man’s Journey</em>, a soul-searching puzzle adventure, tells a story of life, loss, and hope. Interacting with the world around you, you'll shape the landscape to create the old man's path forward. Experience heartache and hope as you embark on a heartfelt journey through a sunkissed world.",
    image: "post/oldmansjourney/oldman.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Puzzle adventure",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Broken Rules",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Old Man",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "MacOS",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "May 17, 2017",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "2 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Beautiful art and cutscenes, story, message",
      },
      {
        question: "Weak Points",
        answer: "Certain parts are a bit slow",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes!",
      },
    ],
  },
  townoflight: {
    quote:
      "12 March 1938, Renée, 16, was ripped out of her world, her only fault was that of not knowing her place in the world.",
    image: "post/townoflight/renee.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Psychological horror walking simulator",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "LKA",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Renée",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "Windows",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Feb 26, 2016",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "3 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer:
          "Flashbacks, challenges the stigma around women and mental health, strong story",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer:
          "Yes, if you can stomach what humans are capable of (and body horror)",
      },
    ],
  },
  emilyisaway: {
    quote:
      "<em class='game-title'>Emily is Away</em> is an interactive story. Create a screenname and choose your path through the branching narrative.",
    image: "post/emilyisaway/screen.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Text-based visual novel",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Kyle Seeley",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Player-insert",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "Windows",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Nov 20, 2015",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "30 minutes",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer:
          "A text-based story, yet done in the most creative and nostalgic way possible",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes, if you enjoy nostalgia and chat logs",
      },
    ],
  },
  nanopesos: {
    quote:
      "<em class='game-title'>Nanopesos</em> is a budget management simulator inspired by the low salaries and high living costs in Chile.",
    image: "post/nanopesos/nanopesos-girl.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Budget management",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Camila Gormaz",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "You, but in Chile",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "Browser",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Nov 5, 2019",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "30 minutes",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Game UI, story, management",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Definitely, especially to understand life on a minimum wage",
      },
    ],
  },
  chicory: {
    quote:
      "You're a dog wielding a magic brush! Use painting powers to explore, solve puzzles and make friends in this top-town adventure game. From creators on Wandersong + Celeste.",
    image: "post/chicory/chicory-dog.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Adventure RPG",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Greg Lobanov",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "You, a dog painter",
      },
      {
        question: "Platforms",
        answer: "Windows, MacOS",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "202X",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "30 minutes",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100% (demo)",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Art, story, game design choices",
      },
      {
        question: "Weak Points",
        answer: "Isn't out yet :(",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "YES, especially if you love art and coloring",
      },
    ],
  },
  welcometoelk: {
    quote:
      "<em class='game-title'>Welcome to Elk</em> is a biographical adventure set on an island like no other, where every character you encounter has a story to tell. From the weird and wonderful to the dark and desperate, all the tales told on Elk are based on true stories of life on the road less traveled.",
    image: "post/welcometoelk/frigg.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Adventure, atmospheric",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Triple Topping",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Frigg, a young carpenter",
      },
      {
        question: "Platforms",
        answer: "Windows, MacOS, Xbox One",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: 2020,
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "25 minutes",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100% (demo)",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Unique art, color design, story, mini-games",
      },
      {
        question: "Weak Points",
        answer: "None! Seriously.",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer:
          "Yes! It's a unique story rich gem with a large variety of story-driven mini-games. What more could I ask for?",
      },
    ],
  },
  forager: {
    quote:
      'The highly popular and quirky "idle game that you want to actively keep playing". Explore, craft, gather & manage resources, find secrets and build your base out of nothing! Buy land to explore and expand!',
    image: "post/forager/forager-dude.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Open world survival craft",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "HopFrog",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "You, the Forager",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "Nintendo Switch",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Apr 18, 2019",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "20 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "99%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Dungeons, expansion system, NPCs, aesthetic",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes, if you don't mind game addiction",
      },
    ],
  },
  firewatch: {
    quote:
      "<em class='game-title'>Firewatch</em> is a mystery set in the Wyoming wilderness, where your only emotional lifeline is the person on the other end of a handheld radio.",
    image: "post/firewatch/firewatch-board.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "First-Person Adventure",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Campo Santo",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Henry",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "Windows",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Feb 9, 2016",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "5 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Art, story, characters",
      },
      {
        question: "Weak Points",
        answer: "Short-lived, rushed ending",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer:
          "Absolutely, but preferably on sale if concerned about game length",
      },
    ],
  },
  sortthecourt: {
    quote:
      "Grow your kingdom by giving your decree in the form of simple yes/no answers.",
    image: "post/sortthecourt/courtqueen.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Simulation",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Graeme Borland",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "The King or Queen",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "Browser",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Dec 14, 2015",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "4 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Cute, relaxed",
      },
      {
        question: "Weak Points",
        answer: "Best suited for mobile, but PC only",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "If you wanna chilllax and rule a monarchy or two",
      },
    ],
  },
  forthepeople: {
    quote:
      "Congratulations, dear comrade! From now on, you are the head of a small but important industrial center bearing the proud name of Iron-1. Your task will be to manage and rebuild it amidst the formation of a new totalitarian regime, currently faced with the consequences of the recent revolution, such as a deepening social crisis and an utter economic deficit. Yet we remain confident that it is young specialists such as yourself, who will lead this county to a stable and prosperous future.",
    image: "post/forthepeople/forthepeople.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Visual novel, strategy, management",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Brezg Studio",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Francis River",
      },
      {
        question: "Platforms",
        answer: "Windows, MacOS, Linux",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Aug 13, 2020",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "1 hour",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100% (demo)",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Story, dialogue, art design",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes",
      },
    ],
  },
  everforward: {
    quote:
      "A girl trapped in a strange world somewhere between reality and imagination. Help her find her way in this adventure puzzle game.",
    image: "post/everforward/maya.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Puzzle, adventure",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Pathea Games",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Maya",
      },
      {
        question: "Platforms",
        answer: "Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, Microsoft Windows, Xbox One",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Aug 13, 2020",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "1 hour",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100% (demo)",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Challenging puzzles, complex story",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes, especially on its release week discount",
      },
    ],
  },
  nightinthewoods: {
    quote:
      "<em class='game-title'>Night in the Woods</em> is an adventure game focused on exploration, story, and character, featuring dozens of characters to meet and lots to do across a lush, vibrant world.",
    image: "post/nightinthewoods/catdrive.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Adventure, atmospheric",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Infinite Fall",
      },
      {
        question: "Publisher",
        answer: "Finji",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: 'Margaret "Mae" Borowski',
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "Windows",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Feb 21, 2017",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "16 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer:
          "Writing, dialogue, story, characters, art, abundance of extra content",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Without a doubt, YES",
      },
    ],
  },
  whenthepastwasaround: {
    quote:
      "<em class='game-title'>When the Past was Around</em> is an adventure point-and-click puzzle game about love, moving on, letting go, and the joy and pain of everything in between.",
    image: "post/whenthepastwasaround/wtpwa.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Point-and-click, puzzle",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Mojiken Studio",
      },
      {
        question: "Publisher",
        answer: "Toge Productions",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Girl and violinist",
      },
      {
        question: "Platforms",
        answer: "Windows, MacOS, Xbox One, Nintendo Switch",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: 2020,
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "15 minutes",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100% (demo)",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Illustration, piano and violin music, symbolism",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer:
          "Yes, especially if you love good art, soft colors, music, and tranquility",
      },
    ],
  },
  venice2089: {
    quote:
      "The city of Venice, once a significant tourism destination but now almost uninhabited, is struggling with the unpredictable behaviour of tides. In <em class='game-title'>Venice 2089</em>, you'll explore the city through the eyes of Nova, a bored teenager who has currently no clue about what to do in life and just wants to relax from the stress of their usual routine.",
    image: "post/venice2089/venice.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Adventure, RPG",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Event Horizon Studios",
      },
      {
        question: "Publisher",
        answer: "Event Horizon Studios",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Nova",
      },
      {
        question: "Platforms",
        answer: "PC",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Aug 6, 2020",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "45 minutes",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100% (demo)",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Music, backgrounds",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes",
      },
    ],
  },
  whenthepastwasaroundfull: {
    quote:
      "When the Past was Around is an adventure point-and-click puzzle game about love, moving on, letting go, and the joy and pain of everything in between.",
    image: "post/whenthepastwasaroundfull/wpwa.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Puzzle, room escape, adventure, story",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Mojiken Studio",
      },
      {
        question: "Publisher",
        answer: "Toge Productions",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Eda and Owl",
      },
      {
        question: "Played On",
        answer: "MacOS",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Sep 22, 2020",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "5 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Illustrations, music, story, puzzles",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes, without a doubt!",
      },
    ],
  },
  rosewater: {
    quote:
      "It's been several years since Harley Leger left New Bretagne and headed west, hoping to leave the past behind and make her way as a freelance writer. After arriving in the sleepy border town of Rosewater, a seemingly trivial assignment for the local paper leads to the hunt for a missing man's fortune - and the story of the century.",
    image: "post/rosewater/rosewater.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Point-and-click adventure",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Grundislav Games",
      },
      {
        question: "Publisher",
        answer: "Application Systems Heidelberg",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Harley Leger",
      },
      {
        question: "Platforms",
        answer: "Windows, MacOS, Linux",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: 2021,
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "1 hour",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100% (demo)",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer:
          "Animation, art style, storytelling, multiple approaches with consequences",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer: "Yes!",
      },
    ],
  },
  unboundworldsapart: {
    quote:
      "Venture into beautiful realities by conjuring magical portals in order to save your kind from the evil that ravage your world.",
    image: "post/unboundworldsapart/soli.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Puzzle platformer, metroidvania",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Alien Pixel Studios",
      },
      {
        question: "Publisher",
        answer: "Alien Pixel Studios",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Soli",
      },
      {
        question: "Platforms",
        answer: "Windows, Mac, Linux",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Q2 2021",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "30 minutes",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Fantastic graphics, fun mechanics",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer:
          "Yes, particularly if youre a fan of beautiful games with fun mechanics!",
      },
    ],
  },
  syberia: {
    quote:
      "Join Kate Walker as she travels to remote locations and time periods in this timeless voyage to discover her true destiny.",
    image: "post/syberia/kate-walker.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "adventure, point-and-click",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Microids",
      },
      {
        question: "Publisher",
        answer: "Microids",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: "Kate Walker",
      },
      {
        question: "Platforms",
        answer: "Nintendo Switch",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: "Apr 20, 2017",
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "5 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100%",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Beautiful music, lovely voice acting, characters",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer:
          "For those of you who love story-heavy puzzle games and a little mystery to your quiet life",
      },
    ],
  },
  lamentum: {
    quote:
      "Guide Victor Hartwell, a young aristocrat on a desperate journey to cure the deadly disease that afflicts his beloved wife, Alissa. Their last hope resides in the darkened halls of Grau Hill Mansion whose Earl has uncovered ancient secrets and forgotten sciences. He claims he can heal Alissa, but… at what price? Grau Hill mansion will open its doors and immerse you in a world of nightmares where you may be trapped forever.",
    image: "post/lamentum/victor-hartwell.webp",
    points: [
      {
        question: "Genre",
        answer: "Action, adventure, survival horror",
      },
      {
        question: "Developer",
        answer: "Obscure Tales",
      },
      {
        question: "Publisher",
        answer: "Another Indie",
      },
      {
        question: "Main Character",
        answer: " Victor Hartwell",
      },
      {
        question: "Platforms",
        answer: "Windows, Playstation 4, Xbox One, Nintendo Switch",
      },
      {
        question: "Release Date",
        answer: 2021,
      },
      {
        question: "Time Spent",
        answer: "45 minutes",
      },
      {
        question: "Completion",
        answer: "100% (demo)",
      },
      {
        question: "Winning Traits",
        answer: "Atmosphere, imagery, sound design",
      },
      {
        question: "Recommended?",
        answer:
          "If you’re a fan of Lovecraftian vibes, chilling atmosphere and gritty horror, yes! Fair warning, it’s not for the faint of heart.",
      },
    ],
  },
}

export default summaries
